So shitty news, or really shitty news?
要听坏消息 还是更坏的消息？
A, the first one.
我选第一个
There's a storm up there.
山上有暴风雪
Well, thanks for the bulletin, Tom, we can't even see the goddamn thing.
哦 汤姆 谢谢你的好心相告 我们根本看不清外面
They won't let us fly up until the weather clears.
他们不准我们飞上去 得等到转晴
Well, when do they expect it to clear?
预计什么时候才能转晴？
Uh, next spring, sometime.
呃 明年春天的某个时候吧
That's the really shitty news, in case you were wondering.
这就是我刚才说的"更坏的消息"
Well, maybe next time.
那就下次吧
Yeah.
好
Next spring.
明年春天…
So now what?
现在怎么办？
Well, maybe your mountain's trying to tell us something.
要我说 也许你的神山想表达一些讯息
What do you mean?
什么意思？
Maybe we've been gone long enough.
也许我们离开太久了
Gone long enough? Gone long enough for whom?
离开太久了？谁离开太久了？
Oh. No, I get it.
哦 我明白你意思了
The mountain isn't telling us it's time for us to go home.
这山想说的 不是让我们回家
The mountain is telling you to tell me it's time for me to go home, right?
而是想让你跟我说 让我回家 对吧？
- Yeah. - You shit.
- 对 - 混账老东西
Why don't you worry about your own, and let me worry about mine, okay?
各人自扫门前雪 休管他人瓦上霜 听见没？
Okay, okay! You don't have to get chippy with me.
好吧 好吧 不用对我心焦气躁的
- What's next? - Next, Hong Kong.
- 下一站是哪儿？- 下一站 香港